Hey, what's up everybody? It's Jeremiah
coming back to you with another video
here in the self-driving car. I want to talk
about something that I've been working with
my clients on in my coaching group. something
that's a topic that comes up often that they
deal with that I think might help you is I find
that people with a lot of skill, a lot of talent,
a lot of ability. They want to do things right
and they want to do things ethical and they
want to do things with integrity. And by the way,
none of that's bad or wrong or anything like like
you should want to do that. Here's the problem.
Because of their need and desire for integrity,
they also put an inordinate fear on people judging
them, thinking that they're doing something wrong.
And let me explain this. When it comes to selling
your courses, your coaching programs online,
you are going to have to paint a picture of the
most positive outcome that somebody can have. And
you want to in your marketing do so as a straight
shot to the overall outcome. So let's say that
you're running a lead magnet that's a free offer.
You want to promise the ultimate outcome. Even if
somebody invested months and months or even years
with you, you want to promise that outcome that
only the top elite 1% of your clients get. Which
means there may be 98% of your paid clients. They
sure they get results, but they not might not get
that ultimate result because of their own choices,
their own decisions and things like that. In your
marketing, you still want to present that ultimate
result. You still want to present that final
outcome as the path that you're helping people on.
And here's the problem that I see a lot of coaches
make. They they make a lead magnet. They make an
offer of some kind, something to generate leads,
and they're only focused on, well, in the lead
magnet, I taught point number one, two, and three
about this topic. And so, in their sales copy and
in their marketing and what they talk about,
they only talk about those little tiny things
that they teach in their lead magnet. And then,
here's what happens. People don't sign up for the
lead magnet. You want to know why? Because it's
not interesting. People don't want information.
They want transformation. They want result.
They want to know that they are going to get
to an end result outcome that is going to change
and transform their life. And any coach who's
worth their salt knows it takes more than just a
30-inute video to change and transform somebody's
life. We all know that. And so sometimes
coaches and mentors who desire integrity,
desire to do the right thing will literally hold
themselves back from reaching the people that they
are meant to reach because they're only talking
about the little tiny thing in their lead magnet
and not the big picture of what working with them.
If somebody became a client with them, if somebody
followed the journey with them, if somebody
went all the way through to the end with them,
you know, if somebody works with me and they go
all the way through to the end of working with me,
I can help them achieve eight figures in their
business. Now, is every client that I have going
to make eight figures? No. In fact, every client
that I have doesn't even make six figures because
some of them literally will not do what I teach.
And this lesson in this video is actually one of
them. I meet a lot of coaches and mentors that
will not and they make it an issue of integrity.
They make it an issue of honesty and it's not. But
inside of them, they have something where they're
afraid of the fraud police scrutinizing them
saying, "Well, you you said I was going to be able
to reach a six-figure goal and you only taught me
the first step of how to get started, so you lied
to me when you created an offer that promised
that." No, that's completely ridiculous. And by
the way, I've created hundreds of offers before.
Never had anybody come to me and say that ever
because I explain it. I explain in the process
that what I'm going to teach you is the steps
to get there. And that if you become a client of
mine, I can walk you through the entire process
of doing so. A single video like this is not going
to make you a multi-millionaire. But I I will tell
you this one concept of getting specific about
the outcome, being bold, audacious about what
you promise people and promising the end result,
the end result that they get to when they go all
the way to the finish line with you, including
paid coaching, retreats, resources, courses,
all of those things. Even if it's just a 30 minute
lead magnet, you want to point a straight shot
in your sales copy, on your landing page, in your
emails, in your marketing all the way to that end
outcome. And that, my friends, is what produces
results. Otherwise, you're choosing to not make
any money in your business. You're choosing
to struggle. You're choosing to not get the
result that you want by stubbornly not following
what I just said. And I have met many coaches who
are so stubborn around this issue that they will
complain and blame and whine about everything else
not working when they're not willing to actually
be bold about what they're promising the outcome
to get for their clients and they're they're
afraid of well I don't want to overpromise and
underdel. Can I tell you this? You should promise
something big and then you should deliver that
big thing to people. And listen, not everybody
because you can't guarantee I you can't hold a
gun to somebody's head and make sure that they
actually do the thing that you say that you're
going to do. But you're going to give them a
process. You're going to give them a step. You're
going to give them a a foundation, an ability, a
skill, something that's going to get them moving
the needle forward, moving the ball forward for
them, that's going to help them reach that goal,
reach that result that they have. And so, listen,
if you're a coach, if you're a mentor, if you're
a trainer, if you're somebody who helps people on
a regular basis get results in their business, and
you show people how to do so effectively, and you
show people what they need to do to accomplish to
reach those goals that they have, you, my friends,
can achieve incredible things in your business.
You can make incredible things happen. You can
reach more clients. You can make more money in
your business than you ever possibly imagined. And
one of the issues is that I meet so many coaches
and mentors that they will hold themselves back
that because they are afraid of, well, I don't
want to overpromise. I don't want to make people
think that something is so possible for them that
it's beyond where they're going to get to. and
they hold themselves back in how they communicate
and how they talk and how they work with people
and how they reach people in their outreach in
their ability to connect with people. And so
if you as a coach, as a mentor decides, listen,
I want to get more results in my business and I
want to create something that leaves a legacy and
I want to impact more people than I ever possibly
imagined. You got to be bold with your offer. You
got to stop holding back on promising something
big. You got to not be afraid to say, "Listen,
I can get you to the finish line here. I can take
you all the way." And then figure out what's your
lane. What's that area that people want to come
to you for? They want to work with you for. They
want to learn from you for and discover what's
possible when you do that. If you're a coach,
if you're a mentor, if you're a trainer, and you
want to know how do I get more clients? How do I
make more money? Jeremiah, can you walk me through
this process of making this work for me? I'd love
for you to join my wealthy coach academy program
to work with us to help you get those results in
your business. I work with people every single
week on their marketing, their sales copy,
their processes, the mindset, everything that it
takes to get there. Click on one of the links in
the description below and I'll see you inside
of our Wealthy Coach Academy program. toxic.